

Senior Web Developer specializing in full stack development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Reactjs, Nextjs, React Native and Nodejs. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

PARAMESHWAR K

Phone:

+91 8778090994

E-Mail:

parameshkrishna98@gmail.com

Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/parameshwar-k

Github:

github.com/Paramesh98

Skill Highlights

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Reactjs
- Redux
- Nextjs
- Nodejs
- MongoDB
- Firebase
- React Native

Languages

English

Experience

09/2021 to present

Web Developer - IBM, India

- Build reusable code that could be utilized in other projects, effectively saving the time and energy.
- Translated concepts into user flows, wireframes and prototypes to promote positive intuitive design, site interactions and user experiences.

08/2019 to 09/2021

Web Developer - Ownerstown, India

- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as challenging back-end server code.
- Utilized Reactjs, Redux for frontend development and Nodejs, MongoDB for backend.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.
- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.
- Work with senior developer to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients.

Education

2015-2019

Bachelor of Engineering: Mechanical Engineering - Anna University, IN.